Guide to the G. William Skinner papers, 1948-1988, 1951-1958 (bulk).
Skinner, G. William papers
- Series IV. 1956-1958, Indonesia
  - Glover - Chinese in Indonesia 1947-1949, Reactions of the Indonesian Chinese to Two Years of Dutch-Indonesian Conflict, 1/10/1950 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Submitted by Clive E. Glover to Dr. de Francis, Course No. 14.303-304, Johns Hopkins University; paper written based on Chinese newspaper excerpts from Indonesia provided by George Kahin.
  - Press Translations (1948-1949) (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Notes from translations of Chinese newspaper articles 1948-49, 2/14/1948-10/13/1949 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Newspaper translations, 5/23/1948-11/12/1948 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - "The Chinese in Purwokerto", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 33)
      Answers to questions of Don E. Willmott supplied by Mr. Siem Tiong Sien
  - Berita Baperki, Berita Baperki various issues, 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Includes: 1954 - 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10-11, 12; 1955 - 1, 2-3, 4, 8, 10, 11; 1956 - 3, 4, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11; Indonesian
  - Berita Baperki Translations, Translations of Berita Baperki articles, 1954 Apr - Oct/Nov (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Includes articles from 1954 - 4, 5, 7, 8, 10/11
  - Other Baperki Materials (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Pamplets, Circa 1955 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Citizenship and elections
    - Interview with Mr. Gouw Yam Hok, 12/11/1956 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - List of Baperki Branches in Indonesia, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Rentjana Perobahan Anggaran Dasar dan Anggaran Rumah Tangga Baperki, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Booklet on proposed changes to the constitution of Baperki.
    - Pedoman Kampanje Perdjoangan Badan Permusjawaratan Kewarganegaraan Indonesia (Baperki) dalam Pemilihan Umum, Circa 1955 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Booklet on guidelines for Baperki’s struggle for change through the general elections
    - Baperki nomor kongres se-Indonesia ke III, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Book on the 3rd Congress of Baperki in Indonesia
    - Siaran and Persibiro Indonesia, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Loose notes, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      No. of votes for Baperki in Java
  - Somers - Baperki in the political arena, Baperki in the political arena 1956-1957, 1960 September (Box 6, Folder 37)
    By Mary F. Somers
  - Associations and their political alignment (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Kuomintang-Communist controversy in Chinese organizations and society in Indonesia, 1956-58 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Write-up from code "S", Circa 1956 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Lists of organizations, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - General Indonesia Data, 1956-57 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Jakarta Data, 1950, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      List of Chinese organizations from 1950 fieldwork; list of Chinese organizations mentioned in press reports.
    - Surabaya Data, 1950, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      List of Chinese organizations from 1950 and 1956-57 fieldwork.
  - Kartomo Project Mechanics (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Letters - Kartomo to Skinner, 6/29/1957, 12/16/1957 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      2 letters
    - Memo to George Kahin, 8/7/1956 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      From Widjojo Nitisastro at University of Indonesia; includes draft questionnaire in English
    - Methodology and Questionnaire, Circa 1957 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      Mostly in Indonesian
    - Report on "The Influence of Chinese and Indians in the Economy of Sulawesi", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 39)
      Indonesian
  - Kartomo Report: Asli-Chinese Relations (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Preface, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Assaat, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Marbangun, 6/7/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Ruslan Abdulgani, 6/12-13/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Mohammad Hatta, 6/13/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Bujung Saleh, 6/17/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Sudjatmoko, 6/18/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Simatupang, 6/25/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Nurhadi, 6/26/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Mardjoko, 7/6/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Hariandja, 8/1/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Tirtodiningrat, 8/20/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Suwirjo, 9/10/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Yunan Nasution, 9/23/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Darsono, 10/2/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Prawoto Mangkusasmito, 10/3/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Suria Atmadja, 10/10/1957 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Intergroup Relations and Citizenship (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Onze Stem, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      Dutch language journal
    - Regulation of the Central War Administrator, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      Banning of newspapers and magazines using script other than Latin, Arabian or Indonesian regional characters.
    - Simposion Baperki tentang Sumbangsih apakah jang dapat diberikan oleh warganegara2 Indonesia keturunan asing kepada pembangunan dan perkembangan kebudajaan nasional Indonesia, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      Available in Kroch library
  - Christianity materials (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Christian groups non-Roman Catholic denominations, etc (as of 1954), Circa 1954/55 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      List of non-Roman Catholic churches in Indonesia, with Chinese-dominated churches marked
    - Apostolic Vicariate Medan, 1955/56 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      statistics
    - Catholics Figures, 1936 and 1955 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - The Indonesian National Council of Churches, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - The Protestant Evangelical Church of Timor, Indonesia, 4/1/1956 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      By Winburn T. Thomas
    - Columbus’ Uncompleted Mission, 1956 July (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Toba Batak Church, 1956 August (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - The Protestant Movement in Indonesia, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      By Winburn T. Thomas; first published in International Review of Missions (June 1953), revised in 1956.
    - The Development of the Program of Cooperative Projects with the Churches of Indonesia, 1956 October (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - The Missionary Commission of the D.G.I., 9/5/1956 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Mass Movements in Eastern Indonesia, 12/1/1956 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - The Church in Indonesia, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      By Dr A.M. Tambunan, Member of Parliament and Vice-Chairman of the Protestant Christian Party (Parkindo).
    - The Christian Movement in Indonesia, 1957? (Box 6, Folder 42)
      Booklet; 40 pp.
  - Statistics - Chinese in the Economy (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Figures on Weaving Industry, 1952; 1957 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - List of Businesses, 1/1/1953 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Figures concerning businesses subjected to the Business Regulation Ordinance, Circa 1956 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Industry figures, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Nomor2 code daerah2, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 43)
      Regional code numbers
  - Population Statistics and Estimates (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Sensus Penduduk 1961, D.C.I. Djakarta Raya (angka-angka tetap), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      Djakarta: Biro Pusat Statistic, 1963, 62 pp.; available in Kroch Library
    - Notes on WNI/WNA distribution in Indonesia, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Population report - Jakarta 1956, 10/10/1956 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Foreign populations in Indonesia, Circa 1957 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      Collated by LTT from newspaper clippings; till end December 1955
    - Official note on Chinese population in Tuban, 2/6/1958 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Chinese population in some cities of Java, 1957 November (Box 6, Folder 44)
      Includes Surabaya,Malang, Besuki, Kediri, Madiun, Bodjonegoro, Madura.
    - Loose notes, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 44)
      With population estimates 1930, 1956.
  - 1930 Census Tables, Volkstelling 1930 - Volume 7 subsidiary tables, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Includes subsidiary tables 6, 7, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 19, 21, 22, 24, 26, 28, 29; translated from Dutch.
  - 1930 Census Translations (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Chapter IV A - The Growth of the Foreign Asiatic Population, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      pp. 39-46
    - HI, 3, A - Chinese, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      pp. 3-7
    - HII, A - Number and Territorial Divisions, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      pp. 9-14
    - Chp VII - Dwellings, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Chp VI A - Civil Condition, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      pp. 69-72
    - Chp V A - Age of the Chinese, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      pp. 50-56
    - Volkstelling Vol XIII p. 15, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Chp VIII A - Speech Groups, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      pp. 86-93
  - 1930 Census Analysis and Reworking (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Maps, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Population breakdown and analysis I, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Population breakdown and analysis II, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Population breakdown and analysis (districts), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Population breakdown and analysis (cities and towns), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Population analysis and code key, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Loose notes I, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ethnic composition (by area), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Loose notes II, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Intermarriage Data, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Chinese intermarriage analysis 1930, Figures and notes on intermarriage based on 1930 Census data, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bandung Population Statistics, Gemeente Bandoeng - Bevolkingsstatistiek 1918-1925, 2/20/1926 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Population Statistics (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Penduduk Indonesia, 2/15/1958 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Published by the Biro Pusat Statistik - Statistik Sosial, Kulturil dan Umum, Seksi Demografi (Indonesia)
    - 1961 Census, 1/5/1962 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      From the American Embassy in Jakarta
    - Registered population, Indonesia (1952, 1955, 1956), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Presented by Biro Pusat Statistik
  - Population Problems (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - The role of transmigration in the redistribution of the population of Indonesia, Circa 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      By Koesman Joesoef; 4 pp.
    - Some aspects and perspectives in the community development of the desa in Indonesia, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      By H. Pattiradjawane; member of Indonesian delegation to Seminar on population in Asia and the Far-East in Bandung on 21 Nov - 3 Dec 1955.
    - United Nations - Seminar on Population (Bandung, Indonesia, Nov 1955), 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition of the Central Resettlement Department at Bandoeng, Circa 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Series V. 1957-1962, 1957 Survey and Early Analysis
  - Questionnaire drafts (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaire for High School Seniors (first draft) I, 1957 April (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaire for High School Seniors (first draft) II, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaire (Chinese), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Don Willmott Questionnaire (Chinese), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Probably original questionnaire from Willmott’s study in Semarang that were forwarded to Skinner.
    - Don Willmott Questionnaire (Indonesian), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Don Willmott Questionnaire (English), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Other early drafts of questionnaire in English, Indonesian and Chinese, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Administration (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Memo to Ministry of Education, 3/25/1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Survey Administration Data, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Includes names of schools and preliminary analysis
    - Letter - Ministry of Education to Schools, 4/1/1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Includes schedule for the administration of the questionnaires
    - Draft survey proposal, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Instructions to Administrators, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Names of student administrators, 1957 April (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Manpower Expenses, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Loose notes I, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Loose notes II, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Discard Analysis, Discard Analysis notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Generation Index Cross-Tabs, Col. 9 (Totok-Per Index) Cross-Tabs, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Tabulation Papers, Loose tabulation sheets, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Coding Plan and Early Marginals (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Column descriptions and basis in questionnaire, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Code Key and Marginals, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Analysis notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Total Deck Marginals, Code Key and Materials, 1962, summer (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Coding - Cols 1-17, Coding notes for columns 1-17, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Also includes col. 44.
  - Coding - Cols 18-23, Coding notes for columns 18-23, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Coding - Cols 24-36, Coding notes for columns 24-36, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Only cols. 29 and 30 included.
  - Coding - Cols 37-44, Coding notes for columns 37-44, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Coding - Cols 45-47, Coding notes for columns 45-47, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Coding - Cols 48-49, Coding notes for columns 48-49, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Coding - Cols 50-58, Coding notes for columns 50-58, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Coding - Cols 59-68, Coding notes for columns 59-68, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Coding - Cols 69-71, Coding notes for columns 69-71, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Coding - Cols 72-80, Coding notes for columns 72-80, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Coding and column changes 1963 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Changes made July 1, 1963, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      An apparent shift of focus to study of sibling position
    - Sibling postion columns, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Reconciliation of Deck 7, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 25)
      On sibling position
    - Coding notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Family values analysis - first runs, Analysis notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Native place - Jakarta students (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Results Schools: A-D only, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - School and Class Identification, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Classification of the Native Places of Overseas Chinese, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Survey Results Analysis Working Notes, Loose working notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Preliminaries to Political Orientation Manuscript (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Preliminary Report on Results of the Questionnaire given to Djakarta High-School Seniors in April 1957, 1958, March (Box 7, Folder 29)
      12 pp., written in Jakarta; includes comments from Mr. The.
    - Contents and Preface, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Preface (Kahin comments), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 29)
      With what is probably George Kahin’s notes in the margins
    - Notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - S & A Journal Club Talk, 10/24/1960 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Title: The Political Orientation of Chinese Youth in Indonesia or Why the Political Sociologist should be an Anthropologist
    - University of Hawaii Seminar, 11/3/1965 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Anthropology department seminar
  - Draft Manuscript - Communism and Chinese Culture in Indonesia (1962) I (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Manuscript (preface & pp. 1-56), 1962 August (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Probably read by Knight Biggerstaff but minimal notes on the margins.
    - Manuscript (pp. 57-117), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Draft Manuscript - Communism and Chinese Culture in Indonesia (1962) II (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Manuscript (pp. 118-175), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Manuscript (pp. 176-229), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Draft Manuscript - Communism and Chinese Culture in Indonesia (1962) III (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Manuscript (pp. 1-56, with comments) I, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Manuscript (pp. 1-56, with comments) II, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Draft Manuscript (Master) (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Pp. 118-175, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Pp. 176-229, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Draft Manuscript (copies) I (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Pp. 118-175, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Pp. 176-229, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Draft Manuscript (copies) II (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Pp. 130-175, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Pp. 176-229, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Other draft manuscripts (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Chinese Kinship change in Java (version I), 1958 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Delivered AAA convention 1958
    - Chinese Kinship change in Java (version II), 1958 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Chinese Kinship change in Java (version III), 1958 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Chinese kinship change loose notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - The Chinese of Java (early draft), 1957 October (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - The Chinese of Java (later draft), 1957 October (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Prepared as discussion paper for Colloquium on Overseas Chinese at American Anthropological Association Meeting in Chicago, December 1957; written in Jakarta.
    - The Chinese Minority in Indonesia - tentative outline, 8/4/1961 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - The Chinese Minority in Indonesia (1963) - draft I, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - The Chinese Minority in Indonesia (1963) - draft II, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 36)
      This was published in a chapter in Indonesia edited by Ruth T. McVey, published in New Haven, Southeast Asia studies, Yale University, by arrangement with HRAF Press [1963]. The chapter constitutes a concise and definitive analysis of Indonesian Chinese by Skinner as a result of his fieldwork from 1956-58.
    - The Chinese Minority in Indonesia (1963) - loose notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Chinese Acculturation in Java (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Draft outline, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Chinese Acculturation in Java (grant proposal), 1963 January (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Request for grant from the National Science Foundation
    - Loose notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Ideas, plans.
  - Hokkien-Javanese Acculturation Analysis (1963), Hokkien-Javan Acculturation Deck Code Key, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Sibling Study Proposal and Notes (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Family Relationships Coding Scheme, 12/6/1969 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - NSF Proposal, 1981 March (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Sibling position and kinship, 1/28/1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Sibling Study (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Sibling Differentiation: Culture and Configuration in Chinese Families, 11/6/1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - All Sibtypes Matrix, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Notes - Family Structure and Politics in Modern China (1975) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Data Run Requests and Code (Oct 1987 - Apr 1988) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Pa-Ch’eng Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 4-19)
    1957 Survey administered to students of Pa-Ch’eng High School in Jakarta; in Chinese.
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1001-1020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1021-1040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1041-1060, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1061-1080, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1081-1100, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1101-1120, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1121-1140, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1141-1160, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1161-1180, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1181-1200, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1201-1220, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1221-1240, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1241-1260, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1261-1280, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1281-1300, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Pa-Ch’eng 1301-1321, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Chung-hua Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, 9, Folder 20-24, 1-10)
    1957 Survey administered to students of Chung-hua High School in Jakarta; in Chinese.
    - Chung-hua 2001-2020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Chung-hua 2021-2040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Chung-hua 2041-2060, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Chung-hua 2061-2080, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Chung-hua 2081-2100, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Chung-hua 2101-2120, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Chung-hua 2121-2140, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Chung-hua 2141-2160, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Chung-hua 2161-2180, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Chung-hua 2181-2200, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Chung-hua 2201-2220, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Chung-hua 2221-2240, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Chung-hua 2241-2260, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Chung-hua 2261-2280, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Chung-hua 2281-2288, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Kao-shang Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 11-16)
    1957 Survey administered to students of Kao-shang High School in Jakarta; in Chinese.
    - Kao-shang 3001-3020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Kao-shang 3021-3040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Kao-shang 3041-3060, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Kao-shang 3061-3080, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Kao-shang 3081-3100, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Kao-shang 3101-3118, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Chung-shan Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 17-22)
    1957 Survey administered to students of Chung-shan High School in Jakarta; in Chinese.
    - Chung-shan 4001-4020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Chung-shan 4021-4040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Chung-shan 4041-4060, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Chung-shan 4061-4080, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Chung-shan 4081-4100, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Chung-shan 4101-4118, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Pa Hwa Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
    1957 Survey administered to students of Pa Hwa High School in Jakarta; in Chinese.
    - Pa Hwa 5001-5020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Pa Hwa 5021-5040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Pa Hwa 5041-5053, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Pa Hwa Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 4-11)
    1957 Survey administered to students of Pa Hwa High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
    - Pa Hwa 5101-5120, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Pa Hwa 5121-5140, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Pa Hwa 5141-5160, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Pa Hwa 5161-5180, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Pa Hwa 5181-5200, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Pa Hwa 5201-5220, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Pa Hwa 5221-5240, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Pa Hwa 5241-5254, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - SMAK Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 12-16)
    1957 Survey administered to students of SMAK High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
    - SMAK 6001-6020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - SMAK 6021-6040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - SMAK 6041-6060, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - SMAK 6061-6080, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - SMAK 6081-6099, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - SMAK I (PSKD) Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 17-19)
    1957 Survey administered to students of SMAK I (PSKD) High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.